ccavenue.ae 2015-03-15

# CCAvenue Privacy Policy – Dubai’s Top Payment Gateway

CCAvenue.ae takes privacy and data protection issues seriously. We have designed this Privacy Policy to explain how we handle personally identifiable information collected from Sub-Merchants who register for services and submit information to CCAvenue.ae through the Internet. As the CCAvenue.ae services evolve, we may revise this policy, so please check back frequently. If you have questions about CCAvenue.ae privacy practices, please contact us at [contact@ccavenue.ae](mailto:contact@ccavenue.ae)

**Scope of this Privacy Policy :**  
This Privacy Policy covers CCAvenue.ae's treatment of personally identifiable information collected from Sub-Merchants who use the CCAvenue.ae payment gateway services, as well as consumer information that we acquire in the course of our business. This Policy also covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that CCavenue.ae's back end technology providers / partners may share with it.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CCAvenue.ae does not own or control or to people that CCavenue.ae does not employ or manage. CCAvenue.ae is a wholly owned subsidiary of Avenues World FZ LLC. This Policy is specific to CCAvenue.ae and does not apply to any other Web sites or Internet services that are part of or to be part of the Avenues Network.

**Objectives:**

CCAvenue.ae respects your privacy and wants to promote trust and confidence on the internet. As such, CCAvenue.ae feels it is necessary to disclose to you what information this site collects and tracks and what we do with the information that we collect.

Information security is critical to our business. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We store information gathered on secure computers. The number of employees involved in the management of the data center that have physical access to these computers is limited. We use advanced security technology to prevent our computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. It is important for you (Sub-Merchant) to protect against unauthorized access to your Login ID/password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and otherwise protect the password used to access the CCAvenue.ae's services.

Currently, CCAvenue.ae collects personal information on our Sub-Merchants, through the Sub-Merchant registration process, the service agreement that they execute and various submitted documents of the Sub-Merchant's creditability as required by CCAvenue from time to time. CCAvenue asks customers to supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name and address, telephone number, and E-mail address. CCAvenue.ae uses this data only for the purpose of filling an order, or communicating with the customer or Sub-Merchant about the status of an order. The Sub-Merchants however, are able to collect personal information on their customers via the purchases that are made. The data CCAvenue.ae collects is used in the aggregate to give us demographic information about the entire CCAvenue.ae audience in order to improve the service to you and to our Sub-Merchants, to perform statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our Sub-Merchants and visitors, to measure overall patron demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the CCAvenue.ae domain and to analyze how and where to use our resources. We use cookies to help us determine which sites users link to, and which services Sub-Merchants and visitors use.

We also track information like the domain name from which you contact us, the pages you request, the products you buy, the referring site, and the time that you spend on the site. For everyone who visits a CCAvenue.ae Sub-Merchant purchase page, we log IP addresses, the type of operating system that your computer uses, and the type of browser software used by you. From the IP address, we can determine the Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of your point of connectivity.

If you are our Sub-Merchant then the personal information you provide - name, address, etc.-allows us to inform you about updates, or changes to the service and to notify you of products and services of CCAvenue.ae, its backend service providers and affiliates that we believe may be of interest to you.

CCAvenue.ae uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and will not disclose this information to other individuals or organizations unless required by law. However CCAvenue.ae will exchange information with other companies and organizations for the sole purposes of fraud protection and risk reduction. However, in the case of abuse or breach of security, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information illegally. CCAvenue.ae will not distribute customer information to be used in mailing lists, surveys, or any other purpose other than what is required to perform our services. However CCAvenue.ae will send personally identifiable information about you (Sub-Merchants) to other companies or people when: 1) we have your consent to share the information; 2) we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 3) we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of CCAvenue.ae to provide a product or service to you (unless we tell you differently these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide them beyond what is necessary to assist us).

Personally identifiable consumer information is also shared with third parties (such as our Acquiring banks and credit card processors) to the extent necessary for CCAvenue.ae to deliver payment processing services.CCAvenue.ae is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers' personal data. CCAvenue.ae may also link to a wide variety of other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

If you (i.e. our Sub-Merchant) would like to view the information we have collected from you and your customers or you want to correct your information or the billing/shipping details of your customers or their IP addresses, Please go to Merchant Login page and log into your account to view the above details and to review your personal information. If you have questions or suggestions, we can be reached by email at [service@ccavenue.ae](mailto:service@ccavenue.ae) or by writing to us at:

**CCAvenue.ae**  
Avenues World FZ-LLC Dubai Internet City,  
Building # 10, Level 3, Office # 313,  
P.O. Box 500416,  
Dubai, United Arab Emirates.

We respond to subpoenas, warrants, or other court orders regarding information that is contained within our access logs concerning any Sub-Merchant, customer or visitor. We reserve the right to release that information concerning any Sub-Merchant who we believe is in violation of our content guidelines, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our servers and services for illegal activities.  
We also reserve the right to report any illegal activity by our Sub-Merchants or their customers to law enforcement for prosecution.

Please be aware that CCAvenue.ae does not control the acts of its Sub-Merchants or visitors. All Sub-Merchants, customers and visitors should be aware that, when they disclose personal information such as their actual name, store's name, e-mail address, etc. to third parties, the information may be collected and used by others to send that person unsolicited e-mail from other parties, outside of CCAvenue.ae. In the event that you encounter any CCAvenue.ae Sub-Merchant who is improperly collecting or using information about users, please contact us by emailing at [contact@ccavenue.ae](mailto:contact@ccavenue.ae)

If you feel that CCAvenue.ae has violated this Statement on Privacy in any way, please contact us at [contact@ccavenue.ae](mailto:contact@ccavenue.ae) that we may address this issue.
